Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Political File, 1924-1953 (Box 99-471)
  - 1938 (Box 106)
    - Campaign, press clippings
      - State
        - Montana
        - Nebraska
        - New Jersey
        - New Mexico
        - New York (Box 108)
          - Metropolitan Area
        - North Carolina
        - Oklahoma
        - Oregon
        - Out-of-State
        - Pennsylvania
        - Rhode Island
        - South Carolina
        - South Dakota
        - Tennessee
        - Texas
        - Utah
        - Vermont
        - Virginia
        - Washington, D. C.
        - West Virginia
      - Ohio counties
        - Adams
        - Allen
        - Ashland
        - Ashtabula
        - Atheus
        - Auglaiye
        - Belmont
        - Brown
        - Butler
        - Carroll
        - Champaign
        - Clark (Box 109)
        - Clement
        - Clinton
        - Columbiana
        - Coshoctan
        - Cranford
        - Cuyahoga, (2 folders)
        - Delaware
        - Erie
        - Fairfield
        - Fayette
        - Franklin
        - Fulton
        - Gallia
        - Greene
        - Hamilton
        - Hancock
        - Hardin
        - Henry
        - Highland
        - Hocking
        - Holmes (Box 110)
        - Huron
        - Jackson
        - Jefferson
        - Knox
        - Lake
        - Lawrence
        - Logan
        - Lorian
        - Lucas
        - Madison
        - Mahoning
        - Marion
        - Medina
        - Meigs
        - Mercer
        - Miami
        - Monroe
        - Montgomery
        - Morgan
        - Morrow
        - Muskingum
        - Paulding
        - Pike
        - Putnam
        - Richland
        - Sandusky
        - Scioto
        - Seneca
        - Stark
        - Summit
        - Trumbull
        - Tuscarawas (Box 111)
        - Union
        - Van Wert
        - Warren
        - Washington
        - Wayne
        - Williams
        - Wood
        - Wyandot
    - Colored activities, (2 folders)
    - Columbia Township, Ohio
    - Contributions, (2 folders)
    - Correspondence
      - “A-B” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “C-O” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 112)
      - “P-Z” miscellaneous, (9 folders) (Box 113)
      - Drafts
      - Form letters
        - Literature, (2 folders)
        - Primary
      - Thank-you letters
    - Cox, Catherine N.
    - Dean, Charles M.
    - Fuller, Inez
    - Election report
    - Final report
    - Ethics statement
    - Finances, (10 folders)
    - Fluhrer, Jack (Box 114)
    - German Groups
    - Good Government League
    - Gradison, Willis D.
    - Hamilton County, Ohio, miscellaneous
    - Harding, Justin W.
    - Information
    - Invitations
    - Katz, Benjamin S.
    - Labor
      - Hale, E. E., (2 folders)
    - Leedle, Arthur (Box 115)
    - Memoranda to Taft, (2 folders)
    - Miscellaneous, primary, (4 folders) (Box 116)
    - Names, (4 folders)
    - National Headquarters
    - Petitions
      - General
      - Circulators (Box 117)
    - Pick Hotels
    - Pledge card lists
    - Polls
    - Primary return
    - Publicity
    - Radio
    - Reardon, William J.
    - Releases
    - Republican Executive Committee, Hamilton County, Ohio, (2 folders)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 118)
    - Schorr, Ed. D.
    - Speakers material
    - Speeches and statements
    - Speeches
    - Statistics
    - Taft letters, (4 folders)
    - Taft-for-Senator Headquarters, counties, (4 folders)
    - Taft campaign before Sept. 1, (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - Taft, Martha Bowers
    - Tallentire, Thomas L., (2 folders)
    - Taxation
    - Tax statements
    - Telegrams
    - Times-Star
    - Township
    - Wilson, Howard
    - Women's groups (Box 120)
    - Young Men's Activities, (2 folders)
  - 1939
    - Postmasters, Ohio, B-W, (2 folders)
    - Post offices, Ohio, B-Z, (2 folders)
  - 1940 (Box 121)
    - State file
      - Alabama
        - General
        - After convention
        - Delegates
      - Alaska, (2 folders)
      - Arizona
        - General
        - Delegates
      - Arkansas
        - General
        - After convention
        - Delegates
      - California
        - General, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 122)
        - After convention
        - Delegates
        - General correspondence
        - Letter to those not on trip
      - Colorado
        - General
        - After convention
        - Delegates
      - Connecticut
      - Delaware
        - General
        - After convention (Box 123)
        - Letter to those not on trip
      - District of Columbia
        - General
        - After convention
      - Florida
        - General, (6 folders)
        - Delegates
        - Letters to those met at Bath and Tennis Club
      - Georgia (Box 124)
        - After convention
        - Delegates
      - Illinois
        - General, (7 folders)
        - After convention
        - Letters to delegates (Box 125)
          - Met at Mid-Day Luncheon Club, Springfield
          - Patterson, Kellogg
          - Rinaker, Samuel M.
          - State senate and others
          - Tavern Club
          - Union League Club
      - Indiana
        - General, (5 folders)
        - After convention
      - Iowa
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Spangler, Harrison E. (Box 126)
        - Starzinger, Vincent, (3 folders)
      - Kansas
      - Kentucky
        - General
        - After convention, (2 folders)
        - Hall's breakfast, (5 folders)
      - Louisiana (Box 127)
        - General
        - After convention
      - Maine
      - Maryland
        - General, (2 folders)
        - After convention
        - Maryland Club
        - Woodmont Rod and Gun Club
    - Minnesota
      - Mississippi (Box 128)
      - Missouri
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Letters to those met at dinner in St. Louis, (2 folders)
      - Montana, (2 folders)
      - Nebraska
        - General, (2 folders)
        - After convention (Box 129)
      - Nevada
      - New Hampshire
      - New Jersey, (4 folders)
      - New York
        - General, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 130)
        - After convention, (2 folders)
        - Buffalo Club, (2 folders)
        - Dinner at court house
        - Hanna's Dan Party, (2 folders)
      - North Carolina (Box 131)
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Lincoln Day Dinner, Greensboro
        - Telegram from Raleigh files
        - Thomson, Charles Dabney, Raleigh
      - North Dakota
        - General
        - After convention
      - Ohio
        - A-B, (4 folders)
        - C-H, (11 folders) (Box 132)
        - H-R, (13 folders) (Box 133)
        - R-W, (10 folders) (Box 134)
        - W, (3 folders) (Box 135)
        - Delegates, (4 folders)
        - Dinner at Deshier, Wallich Hotel, (4 folders)
        - General (Box 136)
        - Just odds and ends, (3 folders)
        - Miscellaneous
        - Queen City Club
      - Oklahoma
      - Oregon
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Letters to those met on trip
      - Pennsylvania
        - General, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 137)
        - After convention
        - Letters to those met at Mr. White's Dinner and Lewis Tea
      - Philippine Islands
      - Puerto Rico
      - South Carolina, (2 folders)
      - South Dakota
      - Tennessee, (2 folders) (Box 138)
      - Texas
        - General, (5 folders)
        - After convention, (2 folders)
      - Utah
      - Vermont
      - Virginia (Box 139)
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Those met at Marion
      - West Virginia
      - Wyoming
      - Wisconsin, (3 folders)
    - Subject file (Box 140)
      - Clippings, (8 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
        - Taft as candidate for president
        - Taft for President clubs
        - Taft's work in Washington, D.C. (Box 141)
      - Comment on speech, (3 folders)
      - Conference notes
      - Congratulations and condolences, replies to
      - Contributions, (3 folders)
      - Conventions
      - Correspondence (Box 142)
        - B-Z, (5 folders)
        - Post election
        - Davis, Forrest, (1 folder) (Box 143)
        - Delegates, (4 folders)
        - Form letters, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 144)
        - Friendly letters
        - Hollister, John B., (4 folders); (10 folders); (5 folders) (Box 145, Box 146)
        - Local politics
        - Negro, (3 folders)
        - Material, Ohio
        - Morris, Edward luncheon
        - Pamphlet file
    - State file (Box 147)
      - Political, general, (3 folders)
      - Poll of delegation
      - Republican National Committee
      - Slogans, (4 folders)
      - Taft letters (Box 148)
      - Taft, Martha Bowers.
      - Taft's Policies
      - Tallentine, Thomas L.
      - Willkie, Wendell L., (3 folders)
        - Presidential campaign
  - 1940-1944 (Box 149)
    - State file
      - Alabama
      - Alaska
      - Arizona
      - Arkansas
      - California, (3 folders)
      - Colorado
      - Connecticut
      - Delaware
      - District of Columbia
        - General
        - Marshall, John, (2 folders)
      - Florida
      - Georgia
      - Hawaii
      - Idaho
      - Illinois
        - General
        - County plan book (Box 150)
        - Faherty, Roger, (2 folders)
        - Patterson, Kellog, (4 folders)
        - Samples of direct mail
      - Indiana
      - Iowa (Box 151)
      - Kansas
      - Kentucky, (2 folders)
      - Louisiana
      - Maine
      - Maryland
      - Massachusetts
      - Michigan
      - Minnesota, (2 folders)
      - Mississippi
      - Missouri
      - Montana
      - Nebraska
      - New Hampshire (Box 152)
      - New Jersey
      - New Mexico
      - New York
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Copies of letters of Taft's trip, (2 folders)
      - North Carolina
      - North Dakota
      - Ohio
        - A-C, (4 folders)
        - D-T, (17 folders) (Box 153)
        - V-Z, (3 folders) (Box 154)
        - County endorsements
        - Taft, Charles P.
        - Taft, Hulbert
        - Walter, Paul, (3 folders)
      - Oklahoma
      - Oregon
      - Pennsylvania, (2 folders)
      - Puerto Rico
      - Rhode Island
      - South Carolina
      - South Dakota
      - Tennessee
      - Texas, (1 folder) (Box 155)
      - Utah
      - Vermont
      - Virgin Islands
      - Virginia
      - Washington, (2 folders)
      - West Virginia
      - Wisconsin
      - Wyoming
    - Subject file
      - Advertisement, (2 folders)
      - Agriculture
      - Armed forces
      - Aviation
      - Ballot count, (8 folders)
      - Bricker, John W. (Box 156)
      - Bills and contributions
      - Broadcast, “Can We Head Off Serious Inflation”, (2 folders)
      - Carothers, Neil
      - Clippings, (5 folders)
      - Congratulations, (2 folders) (Box 157)
      - Constitutional issues
      - Conventions, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Personal
      - Democratic platform
      - Domestic issues
      - Election contests, (2 folders)
      - Endorsements, (2 folders)
      - Faherty, Roger (Box 158)
      - Foreign policy
      - General platform
      - Governors state policy, 1943-1944
      - Harrison, Marvin
      - International trade
      - Labor
        - General
        - CIO and PAC
      - Lists
      - Mackinac Conference domestic, (2 folders)
      - Material, campaign, (3 folders)
      - Minorities
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - Organizations, (2 folders) (Box 159)
      - Patterson, Kellog
      - Pamphlet file, (3 folders)
      - Picknel debates, (3 folders)
      - Picknel debates, (2 folders) (Box 160)
      - Platform material
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Notes
      - Polls and election figures, (4 folders)
      - Polls and forecasts, (3 folders)
      - Republicans (Box 161)
        - General, (6 folders)
        - Cleveland., Ohio, office
        - National committee, (2 folders)
        - National convention, (2 folders)
        - National convention, (3 folders) (Box 162)
        - Platform, (3 folders)
        - Politics, (5 folders)
        - Resolutions committee, (2 folders)
      - Resolutions committee, key men (Box 163)
      - Senatorial committee, (9 folders)
      - Social welfare
      - Sokolsky, George E.
      - Speech comments
      - Suggestions and ideas
      - Survey
      - Taft, Martha Bowers
      - Taft, Robert A.
        - Miscellany, (2 folders)
        - Reservations
        - For president (Box 164)
      - Taft supporters, (2 folders)
      - Taxation
      - Tooze, Walter L.
      - Willkie, Wendell L.
      - Workers, Ohio
  - 1948
    - States file
      - Alabama
        - General correspondence, A-W, (3 folders)
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - National Committeeman
        - South's First Delegate Predicts Taft Victory
      - Alaska, A-Z
      - Arizona
        - General correspondence
          - A-B
          - C-W (Box 165)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - Arkansas
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (2 folders)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - California
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (2 folders)
          - B-D, (8 folders) (Box 166)
          - D-H, (9 folders) (Box 167)
          - H-L, (8 folders) (Box 168)
          - M-S, (9 folders) (Box 169)
          - S-W, (7 folders) (Box 170)
          - Y-Z, (2 folders) (Box 171)
        - Citizens Committee for Taft, Hollywood
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Engagements
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Los Angeles trip, (3 folders)
        - Trips, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 172)
      - Canada, 1947
      - Colorado
        - General correspondence, A-W, (3 folders)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates (Box 173)
        - General
        - Lincoln Day trip
        - Lists
      - Connecticut
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Hartford
        - Lists
        - Literature
      - Delaware (Box 174)
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - District of Columbia
        - General correspondence
          - A-H, (6 folders)
          - I-W, (4 folders) (Box 175)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Miscellaneous
      - Florida
        - General correspondence
          - A-B
          - C-R, (6 folders) (Box 176)
          - S-Z, (3 folders) (Box 177)
        - Clippings
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - Georgia
        - General correspondence
          - A-R, (3 folders)
          - S-Z (Box 178)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - Hawaii
        - A-G
        - Delegates
      - Idaho
        - General correspondence, A-T
        - Boise
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Moscow, 1947, Sept. 29
        - Western trip
      - Illinois
        - General correspondence
          - A
          - B-F, (9 folders) (Box 179)
          - G-Mc, (10 folders) (Box 180)
          - M-S, (8 folders) (Box 181)
          - S-Z, (5 folders) (Box 182)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential (Box 183)
        - Delegates
        - Lincoln Day trip
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Record on mailings
        - Reprint Chicago Tribune
      - Indiana
        - General correspondence
          - A-C
          - D-S, (5 folders) (Box 184)
          - T-Z (Box 185)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lincoln Day trip
        - Lists
      - Iowa
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Delegates
        - Lists (Box 186)
      - Kansas
        - General correspondence, A-Y, (2 folders)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Trip
      - Kentucky
        - General correspondence
          - A-C
          - D-Y, (2 folders) (Box 187)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Literature
      - Louisiana
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Delegates
      - Maine (Box 188)
        - General correspondence, B-T
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - Trip
      - Maryland
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - Massachusetts (Box 189)
        - General correspondence
          - A-Mc, (5 folders)
          - N-Y, (3 folders) (Box 190)
        - Boston trip
        - Clippings
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Literature
      - Michigan
        - General correspondence
          - A-C
          - D-Z, (4 folders) (Box 191)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Detroit trip
        - Lists
      - Minnesota (Box 192)
        - General correspondence, B-Y, (6 folders)
        - Clippings (Box 193)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lincoln Day trip
        - Lists
      - Mississippi
        - General correspondence, A-W
          - Delegates
          - Lists
          - Literature
      - Missouri
        - General correspondence
          - A-B
          - C-M, (5 folders) (Box 194)
          - Mc-Z, (3 folders) (Box 195)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
        - St. Louis
        - Trips
      - Montana
        - General correspondence
          - A-F
          - G-Y (Box 196)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
      - Nebraska
        - General correspondence
          - A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Clippings (Box 197)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lincoln Day trip
        - Lists
        - Taft-for-President Committee
      - Nevada
        - General correspondence, G-M
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Reno
      - New Hampshire
        - General correspondence, C-W
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
      - New Jersey
        - General correspondence
          - A-B
          - C-Y, (5 folders) (Box 198)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates (Box 199)
        - General
        - Lists
        - Trip
      - New Mexico
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Lists
      - New York
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (3 folders)
          - B-E, (5 folders) (Box 200)
          - F-J, (5 folders) (Box 201)
          - K-M, (4 folders) (Box 202)
          - Mc-R, (5 folders) (Box 203)
          - S-V, (5 folders) (Box 204)
          - W-Z, (2 folders) (Box 205)
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - Engagements
        - General
        - Lists
      - North Carolina
        - General correspondence
          - A-P, (2 folders)
          - R-Z (Box 206)
        - Clippings
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Trip
      - North Dakota
        - General correspondence, B-W
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Literature
      - Ohio
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (3 folders)
          - C-G, (5 folders) (Box 207)
          - H-M, (5 folders) (Box 208)
          - Mc-We, (6 folders) (Box 209)
          - Wh-Z (Box 210)
        - City Club, Cleveland
        - Cleveland, St. James Literary Forum
        - Clippings
        - Delegates
        - Engagements
        - Expense accounts
        - Form letters
        - General, (2 folders)
        - General correspondence (Box 211)
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - National defense
        - Presents
        - Publicity
        - Railroad
          - New
          - Old
        - Suggestions concerning the Taft campaign
      - Oklahoma
        - General correspondence
          - A-G
          - H-W, (3 folders) (Box 212)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Tulsa trip
      - Oregon (Box 213)
        - General correspondence, A-W, (3 folders)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Western trip
          - General
          - Portland
      - Pennsylvania (Box 214)
        - General correspondence
          - A-L, (5 folders)
          - M-Z, (5 folders) (Box 215)
        - Bulletin Club Service Bureau, Philadelphia, Pa.
        - Confidential
        - Delegates (Box 216)
        - General
        - Lancaster
        - Lists
        - Philadelphia, Junior Chamber of Commerce and Union League Club
      - Puerto Rico
      - Rhode Island
        - General correspondence, A-Y
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Literature
        - Providence
      - South Carolina
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Delegates (Box 217)
        - Lists
        - Literature
      - South Dakota
        - General correspondence, B-W
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
      - Tennessee
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Delegates (Box 218)
        - Lists
      - Texas
        - General correspondence
          - A-G, (5 folders)
          - H-Z, (6 folders) (Box 219)
        - Confidential (Box 220)
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
      - Utah
        - General correspondence, B-W
        - Clippings
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
      - Vermont
        - General correspondence, B-W
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Middlebury College Conference
      - Virginia
        - General correspondence
          - A-G
          - H-W, (3 folders) (Box 221)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
      - Washington
        - General correspondence
          - A-G, (2 folders)
          - H-Y, (4 folders) (Box 222)
        - Confidential
        - Delegates
        - General (Box 223)
        - Lists
        - Western trip
          - General
          - Seattle
          - Spokane
          - Tacoma
      - West Virginia
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Delegates
        - General
      - Wisconsin
        - General correspondence
          - B-G
          - J-Z (Box 224)
        - Delegates
        - Executives Club, Milwaukee
        - General correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Wyoming (Box 225)
        - Delegates
        - General
        - Lists
        - Western trip
          - Casper
          - Cheyenne
          - General
    - Subject file
      - Brown, Clarence J.
      - Brown, Katharine Kennedy
      - Contributions
        - General correspondence
          - A-E, (2 folders)
          - F-S, (5 folders) (Box 226)
          - T-Z, (2 folders) (Box 227)
          - Miscellaneous
      - Convention arrangements
        - Congressional district map
        - Decorations
        - Election results, (2 folders)
        - Floor plans (Box 228)
        - Foreign
        - “Freedom is a Challenge,” Royalchrome Advertisement series
        - General
        - Gould, Jay, Westinghouse Radio Stations, Fort Wayne, Ind.
        - Handbook
        - Hotel reservations
        - Indiana poll
        - Japp, Matt, Editor, Douglas County
          - Legionnaire, Omaha, Neb.
        - Morrow County Sentinel, Morrow County, Ohio,100th anniversary edition
        - Martin, I. Jack, receipts
        - Miscellaneous
        - Nebraska voting statistics
        - Office supplies
        - Organization outline
        - Personal file (Box 229)